answersafrica.com 2019-11-07

# Privacy Policy - Answers Africa

Answers Africa takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by filling out our contact form when you [click on this link](https://answersafrica.com/contact/)

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our strong commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy only applies to any data gathered on the Answersafrica.com web site (the “Site”), and does not apply to any other information or web site you may be visiting. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This Privacy Policy is effective as of 31st January, 2013. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. You agree that by using the website you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails if subscribed to.

At Answersafrica.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by Answersafrica.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Answersafrica.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable, in other words we know that a user visited but we don’t know who they are

We do not sell our users’ personal information to anyone for any reason what so ever,

 **Google and DoubleClick Dart Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Answersafrica.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Answersafrica.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use such technology in their advertisements and links that appear on Answersafrica.com send directly to an advertisers websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see in order to serve you better.

Answersafrica.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by Google or any 3rd third-party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### If you add content on this site:

When you add any Content to this website: (a) you agree to grant to us a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive  worldwide right and license (including any necessary rights) to publish, reproduce, modify, use, display, adapt, distribute, archive, perform, promote,  translate and create derivative works and compilations, in part or in whole. Such license will apply with respect to any form, media, technology known or later developed; (b) you represent and also warrant that you have all the necessary legal, moral, and other rights that may be needed to grant us with the license set forth in this Section (c) you also acknowledge and agree that we shall have all the necessary rights (but not obligation), using our sole discretion, to refuse to publish, to remove or block access to any Content you provide at any time and for any reason we may decide on with or without notice.

You agree to indemnify and hold us harmless, our subsidiaries, affiliates, related parties, officers, directors, employees, agents, independent contractors, advertisers, partners, and co-branders from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorney’s fees, that may be made by any third party, that is due to or arising out of your conduct or connection with this web site or service, your provision of Content, your violation of this Terms of Use or any other violation of the rights of another person or party.
